but I must part, we get so busy sometimes,
we don't spend quality time with the loved ones,
with people who I'm not saying that,
you know, it's not important to assure dreams or to aim higher,
but I kind of feel like also it's very important
to spend time with loved ones,
to spend quality time, I mean, with loved ones,
because we never know life is short
and that could be the last time I made those people.
I am one of those people who work so hard,
kind of feel like you have to work so hard,
you have to climb to the top of the ladder,
make your family proud, to make the loved ones proud,
but at the same time also those people are getting older,
you know, they're getting younger,
and the more you're busy, also working so hard,
those people also, they're getting older,
and sometimes, you know, we take that time for granted,
we kind of feel like we have, you know, time,
we kind of feel like, you know, we have all the time
in the wall, you know, to be with them,
that someday when we make it, someday when we're successful,
we'll be able to spend time with those people,
but usually that's not what happens,
because for me, Pasal and you know,
I know people who make me who I am today,
but, you know, right now, I can't go where I'm in my life,
but I mean, what's the point of success
if the very people that you want to make proud,
you know, they're all, they passed away,
you know, it doesn't make sense in my opinion.
I feel like it is very important to spend time with family,
spend time with the people that you love,
and for the most part, the loved ones,
the people who truly care about you,
family members, sometimes all what they want is the seal,
to be with you, you know, to love you,
to spend time with you.